Preliminary Inventory of the Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records, 1897-2000 RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.2000.0077, 1977-1997; 20.4 Cubic feet; (17) cartons
  - Project No. 5231: Dormitory Orientation Housing, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 142)
  - Project No. 5209: Contracts and Assignments, 1983 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 143)
  - Project No. 5275: Jones Graduate Tower, 1981 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 144)
  - Project No. 5210: North Area Management, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 145)
- Publications, 1922-1983; 0.25 Cubic feet
  Publications are reports of audits for student organizations and departments. Audits include the spending, payments and money flow for the organization or department.
  - Annual Report of the Auditor of Student Organizations, 1922-1925 (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0005)
  - Annual Report of the Auditor of Student Organizations, 1925-1928 (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0005)
  - Annual Report of the Auditor of Student Organizations, 1928-1930 (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0005)
  - Internal Auditing of Departments, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0005)
  - Executive Summaries: Internal Auditing Reports, 1982-1983 (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0005)
  - Internal Auditing: Registration Services Special Review, undated (Box UA.RG.6.PUB.0043)